Hello, Luisito.
Hello, Torrente.
How are you?
The usual?
Yes, sir.
Another glass?
Another.
Another?
I'm going to take another one.
Another one?
There it is.
What time is it?
It's twelve o'clock.
Another one, Torrente?
No.
I'm done.
Hey, man, I just joined duty this morning.
That's a party...
God damn it, these boys.
God,
damn it.
What a fucking party.
The love, the little turtles.
How is the neighborhood.
What a fucking party.
Hooray!
God, I'm going to die!
How many times do I have to tell you that
selling is illegal?
It can't be sold!
Ambulance sales are illegal!
This is for eating, Mr. Torrante!
I'm sure it's for drugs, eh?
I swear to God that this is...
I swear to the most sacred, you black
bastard!
What do you have here?
My God!
Snacks, booze...
I don't have a choice.
Look, I'm in a good mood.
I wasn't going to stop you.
But of course, I have to give you a little
kiss.
Give me your finger.
No, no!
Yes, the little one.
No, no, no, please.
And I'll confiscate this.
But we are friends, eh?
I'm the state cuba.
This is for you.
Fuel for the body.
Where are you going?
Fuck!
Destination?
Look at the puppies.
This is my Atleti.
The bastards.
The little ones.
You're talking to me, aren't you?
Are you talking to me?
Raffi!
Not me.
He is dead.
Raffi!
Are're you thinking about the cockroaches
or We have the double of Jureles,
man!
You leave it there, now it's my turn.
Come on, get down, it's today.
Mrs. Reme.
Hello.
A revolver-flamethrower of the 38 Special
CGT, capable of piercing a 3 mm steel
plate from 90 meters.
National manufacturing.
Made in Vitoria.
Who the fuck are you?
We are the new neighbors, the fishermen.
Do you like guns?
Would you like to try them?
Yes.
Buy one!
A revolver-flamethrower...
Dad!
What's up?
I'm already here.
That's why I woke up.
Well, you were worried.
I'm always in the middle.
Don't worry.
Bam, bam.
Hey,
be careful, okay?
Calm down, honey, calm down.
Are you going to throw me?
What a delicious kid!
How old is he?
Five years old.
He's so cute, huh?
Have you seen what the lady says to you?
Let's see, what a delicious kid.
Do you like children?
Yes.
If you want, I'll make you one.
I'll smash you!
Don't hit my brother!
Mom!
Forgive the ladies, but...
there are those who have hemorrhoids,
piorrhea, and I have my children.
That's for living.
What a cross!
And you, niece!
What?
Cover your chest.
I don't mind being kicked out of town.
Out.
Always in the middle.
Shut up!
Oh!
It's all right, dad.
I
know you can jerk off, dad.
Oh, well.
I'm not tired.
Careful, dad.
It's just a rough one.
Get down a little, dad, fuck.
Why don't you fix the suspension?
Yes, man, I've got damper brakes,
you know?
My son is good.
Here, dad.
Let's go.
Let's see if you can put an H on my
hemiflash, it seems like I have no
culture.
Yes, man.
If that's what it's all about,
I'm so sorry!
Come on, here we go.
The sun will shine on you.
That hand, that fucking hand.
Remember it, it doesn't look like my
plexiglass.
Sometimes it works.
Don't even think about it.
And don't move until you get what we said.
See you later.
Hi, Felipe.
How's business going?
Bad.
This is bad.
Let's see if...
Oh, sorry.
A lemon, please.
Listen.
I'm worse.
Marcelo!
This is a trap!
Give me the money!
Move!
Don't let him get in!
Come on!
What are you looking at?
Give me the money!
Come on!
I'll shoot you!
Shoot you!
Give me the money!
We told you not to shoot me!
Don't scare me!
Give me the money, man!
Stop screaming!
My brother is crazy, man!
I'll blow your face off, man!
I'll kill you, man!
What's going on?
I don't know.
What's going on, man?
Hello, Torrete.
A good cook to suck your fingers.
Come on.
He gave me some morcilla.
You only put potatoes, man.
Substance!
Come on, fatso.
It's cold!
Those assholes.
Cheers!
Kid, look here.
Come on.
Put the leftovers on that Alván paper,
the aluminum one.
For the dog.
What leftovers?
The one you pick by the table.
What the fuck are you doing?
You're stupid.
Come on.
This neighborhood looks like a nightmare.
I'm telling you, macho.
Full of Chinese people everywhere.
And because of the new restaurant in the
corner.
Chinese, purple, black... and more.
It's really cool.
Here.
The burrito for the boat.
I'll have a whisky.
I owe you 6,000 pesetas of whisky.
But I'm a regular customer.
We're not going to lose a 10-year
friendship for...
6,000 pesetas of whisky.
Fuck, don't fuck with me.
We're going abroad, Antonio.
If you don't pay me tomorrow...
What?
I just ate here.
I'm going to eat somewhere else.
Walk, now.
Or if you get sick, I'll lock you up.
Come on, walk.
Come on.
Come here.
This morning.
I'm sorry.
But it's one's gun.
It's like his dick.
Not anyone can touch it.
That little girl...
Your girlfriend.
Oh, no.
That's my cousin.
The one from the town.
She's a whore.
Whore?
She looks very clean, doesn't she?
It's just...
She's a...
A nymphomaniac.
One of those.
What's your name, man?
Rafael.
Rafael Jiménez Valera.
Well, for my friends, Rafi.
Rafi.
Yes.
Do you like guns?
I think so.
It's just that...
On Sundays, early in the morning...
Yes.
I go to the country house or the park.
I put some cans.
I shoot some shots there.
Fuck.
Free air.
The smell of gunpowder.
A healthy life.
Yes, yes.
Would you like to come?
Fuck, I think so.
Where do you live?
Here, in the first B.
I live in the second.
You and I are going to do great things
together.
Thank you.
Bye.
I have a bite.
I have a bite of ham.
And gabier with chorreras.
A good night.
This is delicious!
Let's see, hand your counts.
A поч Flug.
P. The thing is very bad.
The crisis is very noticeable.
This is bullshit!
Do you dare lie to me?
Probably not.
I를 Hard to give your feedback of it.
Do you want me to register you?
No, no, no...
I have to do this for...
for the tobacco.
Son of a bitch.
The doctor told you you can't smoke.
But a little bit.
Nothing.
Cheers first.
Now you're going to eat this and you're
going to leave the plate clean.
I don't like to fuck.
Come on, enjoy it.
Mr. Torrente.
Hey, Moreno.
What are you doing up so late?
You have to be in bed.
Like the good black people, right?
I come here with some cousins of mine who
want to meet you and thank you for how
good you have been with me.
If not, you shouldn't have bothered,
Moreno.
If I have to, it's my duty.
Don't worry, it's okay.
We're friends.
Calm down.
You can't make fun of each other.
Look at the toilet.
Come on.
What do you
want?
It's Sunday.
Don't you remember?
Sunday?
Clean air, the smell of dust, the shots...
What did you say?
Why didn't your cousin come?
I didn't think about it.
If you give me another one, I'll fuck you
up.
That way, we have someone who won't touch
the cans.
Come here.
Think about it.
For this, what qualities do you have?
It's not like you have to brush your
teeth, huh?
The luck of the beginner.
Look.
Look how a teacher shoots.
It's going to destabilize the bridge.
But I haven't done anything.
You haven't done anything, man.
From what I've said, the gun can't be
touched by anyone.
Now I have to take the review.
You shoot well.
But you're stupid.
You're the number one in my promotion,
fuck.
I've been in the police a lot.
I had two brigades of 50 men at my
service.
And what happened?
In Spain, being a good policeman is very
well seen.
As if it were a crime.
Then you start to get envious.
Enemies everywhere.
They put you in the patrol at night.
Like a novice.
Like an asshole.
I'm sorry, huh?
It's okay.
I still have good confidants.
And when the case comes out that I want,
I'll be bigger again.
What's up?
Do you want to see what I have in my
suitcase?
The truth is that yes.
You'll see.
Look.
An MP28 Smeitzer.
These are no longer manufactured.
You're going to see those fucking cans you
want, Torrente.
What are you doing, man?
Are you crazy?
What's up?
I'm bothering you.
Man, please, have the kids here playing,
for God's sake.
Champion.
In the field of all.
Come on, with the family, circulate.
As soon as they stop right now,
I'll call the police.
And he's going to find out.
Asshole.
What did you call me?
Well, look.
I'm a policeman.
And you're the one who's going to find
out.
But what are you doing?
What a bastard.
Son of a bitch.
That Mond zone man.
And I...
They've already beamed the morning,
kid.
Come, let's go.
They said it's the glasses and they
finally fired me.
But I did wear glasses, kid.
You need to be miope not to see that you
have police jacketande.
You still mind seeing the body,
don't you?
Well, of course.
Hey, Hey, you can carry a soul all day and
use it, and they pay you to do it.
That must be the worst, right?
Well, that's done, kid.
I'll do the filming.
Let's see, what do you do at night?
I can sleep.
You fool, you come with me to patrol.
Really?
Wow.
In two weeks I'll make 18 knollys.
The aperitif is here.
Some berberechitos.
Rafi told me that you are a policeman.
It's a secret, mom, a secret.
My husband, may he rest in peace,
was also a law-abiding man.
He was a conserje before having the
fishmonger.
Then came the robbery, and that was over.
But I wouldn't want to bore you with our
stories.
Thank you, ma'am.
Kid, take the berberecho, it's so fucking
good.
Thank you.
Stay calm, that with me, your family and
your business are safe.
What a man, it's a jewel.
Isn't it?
Amparo, how are you like this?
Don't you see that there is a visit?
Sorry.
Don't worry about me, you are beautiful.
Always in the middle.
Rafi.
José Luis Torrente, to serve you,
at your feet, miss.
For what you like to send.
Excuse me.
Excuse her, she's my niece.
But you know, the girls of now are messy,
they go to yours.
To me, it puts everything lost.
It's very different from my time.
Ma'am, I can use the toilet.
Naturally, but I'm going to put a little
order.
No, don't bother, ma'am.
Be confident.
The second door to the left.
What's up?
My name is Piri.
I have...
Bitch, bitch, get out of there.
Confident, I say.
What a cleaning, ma'am.
In your bathroom you could eat a soup
quietly.
What are you exaggerating, Torrente?
Amparo, are you ready?
Yes.
We have to get there, huh?
Let's go to my nephew's wedding,
who is Hare Krishna, the poor guy.
But he marries as God commands,
for the church.
The other day he stays to eat,
huh?
Of course.
I take your word for it, ma'am.
Yes.
Well, I'm leaving, I don't want to bother.
I'll see you later, boy.
Goodbye.
Bye.
What's up, man?
Antonio.
Now.
Shh, shh.
Chinita, Chinita.
Chinita, come here.
Come here.
What the fuck is this?
I don't like it.
You don't like it?
Well, how am I going to like it?
If this is a courtesan like jam.
Right?
To play tambourine or what?
Bring me blankets.
Bring me a second plate.
Take this.
And bring me bread.
Yes.
Chinita.
Chinita, come here.
What's that on your finger?
It's bamboo.
This is the panda thing.
Yes.
Do I look like a panda?
No.
And bread?
There is no bread.
There's no bread?
Your fucking...
Dispatch.
Come on, dispatcher!
Come on, man!
You're crazy.
You're wasted.
You can't stand it.
I don't know.
That one who is complaining about
everything.
Let's start with him.
Good.
That one on the street.
That one there.
Yes, I can hear you.
A little... a little bit of bread.
Torrente!
Carlitos, what are you doing there?
Watching, as always.
Watch out for the pothole.
Have you seen something weird?
That depends.
Carlitos, I have to go to the daily news.
Okay, okay.
The restaurant.
They don't stop coming in and out all
night.
Are you kidding me?
Yes, and I can also tell you that
something doesn't smell good in there.
The sweet and sour pork.
What else?
There are waste, there are no food scraps.
This is very strange.
Of course, that's because they take
advantage of everything.
For me, they buy the meat in bad
conditions and they eat it at night,
Torrente.
So that the health workers don't find out.
But tonight they're going to end up with
the whole team.
Tonight we have a good job.
We have to go.
Yes, you're right.
You don't drink, do you?
No, no, no.
It's just that it's against Aikido.
I mean, neither tobacco, nor alcohol,
nor drugs, nor ...
Aikido is very bad, huh?
What a fucking idea, man.
What?
The nights are very long.
You have to put on some chuchoncillo.
If it's tonic, you'll be left half drunk.
Do you want?
That's drugs, isn't it?
That's clear.
But it's bad.
What's bad?
Drugs are bad.
Look, here's the drug.
It does something to you.
It bites you, it stings you, it stings
you.
It jumps on you and grabs you by the
balls.
It's going to be a nightmare.
Hello, I'm a drug addict.
I'm sorry to bother you.
This!
This is the bad one!
This is the shit!
Luisito, write this down for me.
Let's take a piss.
Don't you wash your hands?
Later.
Later, later.
Come on, guys.
There are two types of men.
The ones who wash their hands before
peeing and the ones who wash them later.
I wash them first.
Why?
Because my pussy is sacred.
You have to reverence it.
It's the center of the world universe.
The little hose of joy.
You should do the same.
Yes, yes.
Let's go.
You don't know the amount of discrepancies
and microbial microorganisms that there
are in the street to touch it.
You have to respect it.
I don't give a fuck about faggots.
As soon as they touch it, they run to wash
it.
As if it disgusts you.
What a whore you have, huh?
What a gunman, boy.
Thanks.
Have you fucked up?
Fucked up?
Yes, if some whore has already done it.
I haven't.
Fuck.
But I've seen it in movies.
Yes, the one about the cantifla,
right?
I haven't seen it, boy.
It was a joke, I had to eat it,
man.
And what else does it do?
Fuck, how are you going to patrol with me
if you haven't fucked it up?
That way I don't have to respect anyone,
man.
But the girls in the neighborhood...
Ah, nonsense.
Have you changed your underwear?
Yesterday?
Enough.
Come on.
You don't smell like a woman anymore.
Grab the pants, you're going to
hallucinate.
Have you seen what I've won, boy?
Let's go there.
How are the whores, huh?
Come on.
You're going to debut with the most whore.
Boy, give me your card.
Come on, what's going on?
Ready for the papi-topo?
Man, look at Gritos, queen.
Look, look what I've brought you.
Fuck, is the circus arriving in the city
or have they left the monkeys' cage open?
Fuck, hey, don't scare me, I have a little
problem.
If it were just one.
What a bitch, you're going to demotivate
me.
Look, Gritos, I've brought you a child.
Give me back a man.
Come on, let's go upstairs, to the middle.
And behave like a cop, damn it.
Girls, bye.
What the fuck,
wait.
Aren't you ever going to take off your
clothes?
I'm embarrassed.
What's wrong, am I going to have to
undress you?
I...
Fuck.
Come on, Nene, it's for today.
I charge for hours.
So you've never had sex, huh?
No.
But I've seen it in movies.
Oh, how nice!
How sweet.
Well, it might give you a little
impression.
Come on, come closer.
What?
Aren't you going to bite?
Come on.
Come on!
Wolf!
You like them, don't you?
Yes?
So, that's it!
Get dressed!
See how easy it is?
And this is not even a word to the fat
guy, eh?
Damn, man!
So fast downloading!
How is it?
A great pleasure, isn't it?
This is a man!
It's a piece of cake!
This champion...
What a hand you have, eh?
Yes, yes, you do have it, yes.
Well, and mine?
I invite you to this.
Do you have some tangerines over there?
It's the payment for the week.
Man, man, man, man!
What the hell is going on here?
Here you don't have to scat, fuck!
Don't be a rat, fuck!
Come on, get ready.
Here are the tangerines.
What the fuck!
What do you have there?
You have to pay for them!
Fuck, bravo!
Come on!
What have you done?
Bye, girls!
Hey, Loma!
Girls, there has been no luck.
Go to Torrente!
Come on!
This is the place I told you about.
And now nothing.
To watch out in case we see something
strange.
This is the worst thing about being a cop.
Until something happens, it's a pain in
the ass.
We'll make some tangerines.
Some birds, I tell you.
You and me?
Of course, man.
Now?
Look, if it's to give us a taste.
You give me the money, I give you the
money.
To relieve tensions.
No bullshit, huh?
No bullshit.
I don't know if it's going to be now.
Come on, get out of here, man.
If it's to make time, come here.
You can't be here.
Why not?
It's a private place.
All the street?
Yes, our street.
And we don't want fat assholes.
What have you done?
It seems to me that you are wrong,
huh?
Look.
I'm going to leave.
But because I want to, huh?
Are you going to let them kick us out like
that?
Calm down, kid.
Let him trust himself.
Do you trust me?
Five motorcycles full of Chinese?
They will be food distributors at home.
At 4 in the morning?
Here in the house, kid.
Here in the house.
I don't like this place.
Here there is no environment.
I like it in a square near the market.
Or in a high school where children pass by
that are tremendous.
You are a whore, dad, fuck.
You take a capricious.
Do you see this Chinese guy?
Yes.
It's a vigilance mission.
You have to see if something strange
happens.
Don't take your eyes off him.
Come on, man.
It's nothing.
What a disgrace.
How could this happen?
No.
He has to go.
He has to go to work.
Come on, man.
It's nothing.
What a disgrace.
You are a neighbor.
You have to be brave.
You said this would take him a second to
recover.
Don't you think about such things?
I'm Amparito.
I've been taking care of my father for all
my life.
For this.
It's better if I go home and rest.
I just want to pray, pray a lot.
I'm broken, man.
I'm going to go up to the house.
The walls are going to come up.
Come on, man.
As soon as I change, I'll go up to
accompany you and I'll bring you some
dinner.
What do you think?
What am I going to think, Aparito?
That you are your angel.
Aparito!
Come in, come in.
Well, this is you.
Impressive, huh?
And this little beast, how does it smell?
Look, I've prepared four silly things.
You deserve this and more.
This was delicious.
I put it in purple.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
This was delicious.
I'm glad you like it.
Pretty, clean and knowing how to prepare
soup, the perfect woman.
Come on, man.
If I got married, I would be with a woman
like you.
Aparito, I want to show you something.
What?
You'll see, what a surprise.
Look.
What?
Do you like it?
How is it?
It's for me.
Sure.
I don't know many Aparitos.
I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything.
Goyanes made it for me.
The cantinero de la Mili.
He took me 6,000 pesos, bastard.
This gives me a little shame.
But I would do it.
Don't look for more.
Come on, these are my aunt's jokes.
She's been looking for you all day.
Damn.
It's not good to go out there doing crazy
things.
And less at her age.
At my age?
If I'm a kid.
This little girl, huh?
Who is this little girl from?
Little girl.
Aparito, damn.
Don't be a playboy.
I'm going to put some music on.
Bitch.
The You liked it, huh?
Gotta be one of the best dusts of my life.
Come on, without paying.
How can you do without paying?
Open the door, you bitch.
Torrente.
Uncle Rabbi.
Hello.
Sorry, if I bother you...
No, you don't bother me.
But you see, maybe we end up being part of
the family.
I came so you wouldn't forget about the
round.
Fuck, the round.
The call of duty.
Chata!
What?
Before you go, pick up your little things.
Come on.
How did I put your cousin?
You're such an asshole.
So they were your father's?
Yes.
Remember the special case I told you
about?
The one I need to get back the job I
deserve.
Yes.
It's this one.
You just have to go in there.
In the restaurant?
In the restaurant in La Tapadera.
And what do you want us to do,
now?
Now, now, with a pair.
But you and I alone?
Are you fucking kidding me?
If you want you can go, I don't need you
for anything.
No, no, that's not it.
Me with you, where do I need to go?
I say it because of the macarras at the
door and that.
Yes, the truth is that we don't get along.
They put it the other day.
Besides, have you seen my car?
The van, that one from the fishery,
is yours.
It's a fucking camouflage.
Bring the keys.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's just that my mother is still paying
for it.
And she also told me that I only use it in
the ports.
But what do you want, kid?
That you look so pure?
Put in subordination.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go for her.
The keys.
Torrente.
The thugs from the other day.
Fuck.
What do we do?
Come on, let's go.
The cops, come on, see you in a minute.
At least this will give you your phone a
newERS- Where?
I don't fucking know.
Who are you fucking with, man?
We're not playing withurs, man,
we're just trying to be looking for
directions.
Fuck.
Well, good night.
He took off his glasses and was fucking
barefoot, didn't he?
Okay, thing goes like this.
Shit, shit...
What have you done?
I thought you were already ready for this.
You've got After Dark.
What have you done?
It's very dark, isn't it?
Come on, kid, be a coward.
If you go first, I can cover you.
Stay very close, I don't know what's wrong
with you.
So you don't know where Enrique is?
No, I don't know anything, I don't know
anything.
Hey, I'm a calm man, reasonable.
Sometimes I have my ups and downs,
like everyone else.
No, no.
But it seems to me that today I'm behaving
well.
It's true that I don't know anything.
Then why do I have the feeling that you
are laughing at me?
I don't know anything, leave me alone,
please.
You are telling us a story.
I don't know anything.
A Chinese story.
I don't know anything, please.
And Chinese stories are told to children
and assholes.
Do I look like a child?
No.
Hey, do you think I'm an asshole?
No, no, no.
You see?
You are insulting me.
And that hurts me.
I understand.
A Chinese.
A beautiful Chinese.
Please, leave me alone.
Explain it, Israel.
No.
It wasn't me.
He's the one who bothers me the most.
What's up?
Hey, Chinese.
Do you understand?
Don't you like it?
I don't know anything I don't understand
you, follow me.
Alright, 65 Yuca سbbс Mulman.
This doesn't go on like this anymore.
No, no!
Come on, the direction is over.
Clean up too.
And you, to work.
Has my uncle Mendoza called?
Yes, good news.
What does he tell me?
Have Farrelly rolled up?
Well, yes.
Leave us the complete Birmano lot,
for 50 kilos.
Only 50 kilos?
But not of the highest quality.
In your fucking life I have seen a heroine
like that.
As soon as I found her...
We are going to be the kings.
We are going to get ten times her value.
Fuck.
When is the delivery?
Wednesday night.
But on Wednesday we would have an orgy
with the travestis.
Fuck, then you will replace her.
Come on, come on.
The hand.
The nails.
For such a stupidity we could die.
We have to leave no clue.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Quiet, guys, the channel in the pit.
I fuck the city up by the hand.
Fuck, if you want to go faster,
get down and run, because this is not the
early dawn.
The mother who killed us.
It's fucking his mother.
What are you doing?
Calmly, calmly.
Fuck, they will fuck us, they will fuck
us.
Torrente, we're going in a forbidden
direction.
It was the guy.
Fuck.
Come on, come on!
Yes, yes, we didn't have to get hurt.
Shut up, Rolfi, don't be a jerk,
damn it!
They're going to hit us!
They're going to hit us in the end!
They're still there!
You'll see, kid!
I'll fly up and lose them!
Hold on!
What's this?
The street is cut off!
Fuck!
This wasn't here before!
Socialist extortion!
Socialist, come and give us your
permission!
They got off the bikes!
Calm down, kids!
We have to think of something!
We're going to die!
No, no!
Take that shoe, Torrente!
Take that, Jeroboam!
There it is!
We're saved!
Aah!
And the duck had four beautiful little
ducks!
But after breaking the last one's shell...
What a ugly little duck!
When Mama Duck swam with her children,
all the animals of the farm stared at
them.
Say!
Sorry to bother you at this time,
but we have a problem.
I have told you a thousand times not to
call me this number.
Someone has entered my office.
Damn it.
The Colombians?
What were they?
Colombians?
No, they told me they were a fat man and a
normal man.
Two strangers.
They don't look like professionals.
I don't like this.
I don't like anything.
Dismantle everything.
We will set up another laboratory after
the delivery.
That's right.
That's how it will be.
What's going on?
Dad, and the story?
The story?
Well, they took him to a restaurant in El
Pacito and they turned him into an orange.
Dad, the story doesn't end like that.
The story ends as if dad gets out of his
ass.
Go to sleep.
Wow, what a horror.
The one who has his mouth like grass.
How do you know?
It happened to me when I saw my first
dead.
Those people are incredible.
They have charged a Chinese.
The worst thing has been the van.
I'm going to see how it goes with my
mother.
Don't think about that now, to be sure.
We have to call for reinforcements as soon
as possible.
What did you say?
That we have to call for reinforcements.
Get rid of it, kid.
This is the case of the century.
What do you want?
That the first Inspector Listillo doesn't
step on it?
We are going to solve it ourselves.
Yes, how?
Well, you will have to look for people,
maybe, yes, but people from the street.
Patriots!
I have some friends.
I go with them to the gym and so on,
to the villas.
Tomorrow I will stay with them to go to
play the role.
If you want, we can tell them.
Who are they?
Just like you.
What are you talking about?
Look who's here.
Hi guys, I'm Torrente.
Raffi has already told me that you are
tough guys.
Hey, little brother, don't worry,
this is Torrente, man.
Is this the one with the machine gun?
Don't fuck with me.
What's up?
Hasn't Raffi explained what I am?
Yes, a piece of shit.
Respect, guys, I have a gun.
Come on, to the street.
I want to explain a little thing to you.
You have to help Raffi and me.
Are you angry or what?
Let's see if we are going to follow a
fucking fat guy like you.
Don't get me wrong, eh?
That's true, Raffi, you can't get any
cooler than an eight.
He's asking for bad things, the disgusting
guy.
Well, call for more respect.
Guys, guys, we're going to have it,
eh?
Be careful with me, I don't know who...
Hey, hey, son.
What?
You pushed me.
If you can be more careful.
If you can...
You're dead, son of a bitch.
Cut!
No, Michelin, what's wrong with you?
You don't know who I am, do you?
You are Policarpo Díaz.
El Potro de Vallecas.
The biggest pugil in all of Europe.
58 victories per KO.
Besides, you're going to be a world
champion.
Torrente tells you so.
There you go, you know all my records.
And on top of that, from the Lety.
Throw it, please, come on.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, come on.
You, Sultan.
Fuck, you could have hit yourself for
money, man, in the ring.
It's just that the one you hit yourself...
Wow, what a bad blow to the head.
Let's go and help your friend,
man.
What do you think you're doing?
Right.
You and I are going to make history.
And without a piece of training.
Talk to us.
Of course.
And for that I have to get to know you a
little better.
Know your aptitudes.
Because I'm going to make men out of you.
What's up, kid?
Aren't you interested in what I'm saying
or what?
Let's see, what do you know how to do?
Well, I'm an expert in 007.
And what's that?
Erotic telephone?
No, man, no.
The super spy.
Yes, Heinz Bond.
The number one.
Well, after me.
Because I've worked for the CIA.
I already said that.
And he's my cousin's boyfriend.
Well, to me, in reality, from espionage,
the part that I like the most is that of
computer science, you know?
The fireman is a monster.
He studies F.P.
Because of the branch of electronics.
Very good.
It's never too bad to have an intellectual
under the command.
And Malaguita is a brown belt.
I don't know for black this year.
Well, you've seen all those of Jackie
Chan, Bruce Lee and that of the sea.
Dacascos.
Sea of Dacascos.
The new boom in the world of martial arts.
Have you seen that of the strongest?
33.
The slingshot.
The eye of Jane.
The double strike.
The blow-up.
The golden shield.
I too was agile in my youth, and I didn't
do so much.
It was all fiber.
But look, then, with the experience I
have, karate, chuchichu, is not worth
anything.
A good kick, the fess.
In fact, fucking a good kick.
No one can kick me in the balls.
From a lateral and flexed position,
closing the waist and with a hip twist...
BAM!
Demonstration.
Try to kick me, Torrente.
Try it.
This guy here is a bit of a ghost.
I don't think so.
Come on, come on.
I'm going to make you look funny,
kid.
I can't, I'm trained.
Besides, this posture with the right
concentration helps the ki to introduce
the genitals and the scrotum into the
peritoneum, giving the consistency of a
wooden board.
You'll see where I put the scrotum.
Bingo!
Come on, let's go, guys.
On the street.
Admission is paid to you.
This is not what you think it is,
kid.
This is a modern shit.
Your style of bingo, or what?
Kid, you're giving me a lot of trouble.
That doesn't go anywhere, man.
I'll take care of it.
Chata, not more than that.
They make you look funny, these ladies.
The cameramen?
No, fuck, the whores.
It is that...
when I see one, I think they fucked her
up.
This one, for example.
This one is egged.
They've got them, they've run away,
they've left the group inside.
If not, what the fuck?
Enough of that shit.
Thinking about this bullshit makes me
sick.
Don't fall down, there's a place here.
Fucker.
Fuck...
This girl, you like her ass.
I'm telling you.
But, Torrente, do you believe her?
She must be 13 years old or very young.
I don't know, very tiki-tiki, right?
Yes, having menstruated.
You're ready to go to the ITV.
Hello, Torrente, I'm going to call by
phone, my mother is worried.
Come on, you have to be a good son,
come on.
This is the situation, guys.
Rafa and I are following some super drug
traffickers.
They are about to receive a huge,
very pure heroin dose.
We have been to their lab, their
headquarters.
We know when the delivery will be.
What we don't know yet is where.
And that's what we have to find out.
Let's see, the cubes you ordered.
Chuchu.
Silly ass.
How did you get there?
Torrente, good news.
My mother says her father has recovered,
he's at home.
Okay, okay, crazy, but we have to do what
we have to do.
Now that we are focused on the plan.
Ah.
Sir.
I can put a microphone in there.
A microphone?
An infiltrated spy?
Hey, 007, man.
That's what I want.
Fuck, of course.
And also, by sticking a cell phone to the
microphone you will carry, we can hear
everything from the outside.
That's the best way to find out.
Perfect, Rafi.
We already have a plan.
Tomorrow is going to be a big day,
guys.
There we are.
Come on.
Whisky is one of the things that has the
most vitamins.
Hey, your colleagues are crazy,
thank God.
Good evening, Torrente, and the company.
Good evening, Favel.
Can I sit down?
If you get to the tower...
What a game you have lost, Torrente.
The Athletic has given an impressive
review of Real Madrid.
How can it be?
Drink my colors.
I, for the Athletic, give my life.
You are lucky, guys.
There is nothing bigger than working with
Torrente.
This man, wherever you see him,
is number one.
The best.
Here you go.
A little gift for you, for you and for all
the people.
Very good, Carlitos.
Come on, come on.
You.
I'm going to continue with the patch.
And there's still a lot of money out
there.
Of course, of course.
Be careful, don't get off your feet.
Torrente, if this is before yesterday...
If it was not for Torrente, I would have
gone to the beach, but I'm not going to
bring a donkey.
Another round.
Come on.
Let's go to lunch.
There they put a song about the donkey.
We have never been left out, but with
you...
I hope you guys get into real peace.
Come on, fuckers.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Boy, for a little good music.
What are you doing here?
You can't be here.
And what the fuck is this shit?
Get out of here, man, just leave.
Wash your mouth before you talk about gay.
Fuck.
And in addition to bravery, he looks like
Don Juan.
Come on.
Come on, let's have another one.
There's a place in Guarra that I know
around here.
Let's go!
You're going to forgive me, but I have to
go.
It's late, I have to go to work tomorrow.
Us too.
Work!
Come on, let's go to work.
Let's go, Rafi.
I think I have to go to work.
Also, remember that tomorrow we have to go
with the plan, why don't we go home now?
Go with your friends, come on.
Don't let them get lost.
Why don't you come, Tarranté?
See you tomorrow, huh?
Hello,
mother!
Hello, Chippo!
We are very lucky!
Tarranté...
I don't see him anymore.
Come on, man.
The penultimate, Luisito.
No, no, no.
Go to his house.
You go with me.
It's soon.
No, no, no.
Come on, man.
Are you my friend or not?
Yes, man.
I'm his friend, but...
This gesture...
This is too much.
Come on, Luisito.
Come on.
Come on, man.
Give me another one.
Come on.
Luisito!
I'll get the pencil.
Juan, we have to leave.
He is tea the opposite.
Of course.
Does not there have to be tea much much.
If you can put another one, take it.
Hi.
Do you like what you brought mom?
This is...
I'm going to have a cafe.
If you like anything, then WhatsApp,
it will be advisable.
in ten days.
Here.
Tell me everything, eh?
Have a nice day.
caso...
No, no, no.
Today, every day to ride a bike.
Well, because you've been bad.
Bad?
Don't worry.
What are you doing, you bastard?
Since I started, I have a balance.
I walk and I feel better.
What do you want?
Do you want a neighbor to see you?
Sit down!
Don't you realize that if the social
assistant finds out, he'll fuck us up.
So what are we going to live?
Don't you dare get up again, huh?
Hey, Dad.
What about the bicycles?
I think I can sell them, damn it.
Come on, give me the bills.
Come on!
Come on, go fuck yourself.
Hello?
There's no one here!
Corrente, come on, we're all here.
How are you, guys?
Is everything all right?
Categorically.
The sound is a bit shabby, but it's well
received, huh?
Damn, there was nothing bigger.
What if it's the last microtransmission?
Well, with the cap you can't tell.
Nothing.
Kid, the plan.
You have to go to the restaurant.
And once there, you ask for the boss.
Then you say that he's one of Farrelly's
men and that you come to confirm the data
of the delivery.
Okay.
So I'm going to deliver some data to
Farrelly, right?
No, no, no, no, no.
You have to confirm the data of the
delivery and you come from Farrelly.
Let's confirm the delivery data.
Above all, don't forget where,
the place where the delivery took place.
Okay.
Let me go there.
Just push this button.
All right.
I push the button and say I'm... from...
Manili?
Farrelly, kid.
Farrelly.
To confirm the data.
Well, that I'm part of Farrelly and that I
am told where the data will be,
right?
Where is the delivery going to be?
I see you have it clear.
No doubt, right?
None, none.
Don't you prefer me to go?
I don't know.
I, in dangerous situations, know how to
react.
Demonstration.
Fuck, Malaguita!
Yes?
Mendoza, this is Lefrances.
We are waiting for instructions.
Farrelly called me five minutes ago.
The delivery will be tonight.
In the old warehouse.
Everything ready?
No problem.
Have you heard anything from that
gentooza?
Not yet, sir.
Anyway, take precautions.
I want all the men ready.
Understood?
All the men ready.
Of course.
I'm not going to let those sons of bitches
spoil my business.
Tell the boss what can happen.
Thank you.
Good luck, kid.
Torrente, there's something I don't
understand.
Why did we put a microphone on him?
Can he tell us when he comes back?
Better the first-hand information.
Besides, who the fuck guarantees he'll
come back?
Come in, come in, kid.
Good afternoon.
Come in.
You came from Farrelly?
Yes, I'm a Farrelly man.
He sent me to talk about the exact place
of delivery, the drug thing.
Here, take a bottle of caddy.
Thank you.
Sit down, sit down.
Can I have two?
My mother says sugar is the food of the
brain.
This Torrente is a bit silly, isn't he?
That's right.
A boy who pays attention to his mother
will surely be a boy with no problems.
Problems?
And what?
Have you been working for Farrelly for a
long time?
Yes, I mean, no, Manili, that is,
Farrelly, has me to test.
It's a summer program, a couple of months
and I'm drunk.
I'm glad, man, I'm glad.
And tell me, what's good about Farrelly?
I imagine he will continue in Segovia,
getting fed up with Cochinillo.
Yes, yes, he gets blind.
Really?
I'm glad.
What did I tell you?
I already knew that Farrelly had not
become vegetarian.
Villas, this smells disgusting,
man.
What are you doing there, bastard?
It's to hear the game.
I'm going to tear your eyes out.
Send me Torrente.
You're a chivato.
Tell us everything.
We just need to give him our address.
Torrente is Rafi's friend, the fisherman.
He's his cousin's boyfriend.
He's a bastard.
I'm a kid, I don't want to die.
Are you being serious?
Guys!
Lenny, Lenny, fuck!
Tonetti, fuck!
Tonetti!
What's wrong?
Pluck that crap off there for ever!
I don't see any traces...
He's dead...
He's dead!
Fuck, Tonetti!
Nettie!
This is so bad, Nettie.
Hey, hey, hey, don't cry like assholes.
You saw what was coming, damn it.
This is not Bambi.
But, well...
He was our friend.
He was a softie.
If Adam was my first exchange student.
But here they were going to torture him.
Torture him?
And what the hell is going on?
When I was in the Legion, in the Africa
Corps, we spent months in the desert.
And it was so hot that we would burn our
mouths in the jeep's body.
The scorpions would bite us in the balls.
We had fevers, typhus.
The dog was even a puppy.
And the Moors, who are like French,
but dirty, ate Palomeque and his dog
alive.
Why were we there?
Because we didn't want to tell a friend.
Because we had patience.
Patience, guys.
Patience.
You... you were a softie.
Yes, he was a softie, yes.
A softie.
Hey, Torrente, could it be José Luis
Torrente?
Do you know him?
What do you know about that?
Well, at first I didn't care, but this
morning in the warehouse I found this.
Rodrigo, if you had a melon in your head,
wouldn't you be dumber?
Who hired you this subnormal?
That's the wine from Mendoza.
Fuck.
But you're stupid.
But you don't know how to read.
As I was old, I didn't think...
A cop took us out at home and as if
nothing.
What did you call Padilla today?
To earn his salary.
Fuck.
Memo.
With Commissioner Padilla.
Oh, sorry.
Come on.
Olano.
There.
Quiet on the ground!
Take a look.
Where is he?
Who?
José Luis Torrente.
Where is he?
What he has done is very bad.
He broke my bike.
Where is he?
I tell you it's very bad.
I've been doing it all day.
Fuck.
Where do these people come from?
There is no one here.
And now what do we do?
Let's talk.
Honey, open.
It's me.
Amparín.
Not a word.
Have you heard me?
Come on.
Who are you?
A neighbor.
Don't tell me you were coming for parsley.
I come to pick up a tray.
And that someone has to die for a tray.
Die?
Look, I don't know what all this is about.
But I'll do whatever it takes.
Say.
What do you know about Torrente?
Nothing.
He is a friend of my cousin Rafi.
He told us that he was the boyfriend of
his cousin.
Yes?
Look, I am not the girlfriend of anyone
but that person.
For me, as if they want to take care of
him.
You are going to come with us.
That, that.
We need to relieve certain body tensions.
And you have very beautiful lips.
If what they want is that I suck it.
And I suck it.
That would be fine, boss.
To relax.
If you want, we can do it right here.
Come on.
Get out of here.
Relax.
If you are going to suck it.
Sorry.
I mean, if they are going to suck it.
Let's see if they can give me a pass too.
Grandfather, don't say crap.
And keep the chicken.
You are a macho.
You are going to be a faggot.
Faggot?
Have you called me a faggot?
Leave it, man.
You are very old.
Don't hit that woman.
Hit me.
Come on.
And shine in front of your friends.
Take out the gun.
And say stop.
Well, if the gun is not a toy.
What did you think?
That I was going to kneel down with those
girls to ask for forgiveness?
Son of a bitch, Enrique.
Wow.
We have a champion grandfather.
What?
Do you feel like a champion?
Do you want to fight, grandfather?
Come on, grandfather.
Come on.
That's it.
Like this.
All right, grandfather.
On your side, grandfather.
Ouch, what a damage.
Break me, grandfather.
Let's see.
I was wrong.
I was wrong with you.
I thought you were traitors.
But I am...
Three sons of bitches.
A little bit of respect, grandfather.
I'm going to kill myself.
Leave it, man.
Don't see that he is dead of fear.
Fear.
And I... and you...
Take the girl.
It was horrible what happened to your
father, Mr. Torrente.
And those gentlemen, who were three,
and they dragged my poor niece.
Bastards!
And they left this note.
Stay away, garbage, or she will die,
the Frenchman.
Garbage?
My poor niece, kidnapped.
Yes, she is a saint, and you appreciate
her very much.
I appreciate her?
Yes, yesterday she told me that you are a
very attractive man.
Torrente, look who I brought you.
This girl?
Chinita, Chinita, do you remember?
This is the Chinese woman from the
restaurant.
Yes, the Frenchman and his men are very
bad.
He killed his father, he killed my
boyfriend.
I repeated one.
I want to avenge myself.
I know everything.
I decided to go to you, so you can avenge
Juan.
Do you know where the delivery is going to
be?
Yes, yes.
Tonight, in the old warehouse.
Maybe it's a trap.
No, no, no.
I'm going with you.
And if it's a trap, I'm going to die.
Guys, for my father.
For Torrente.
For Juan.
And for my cousin.
Come on, I'm going to get you.
Yes, yes, I'm going to get you.
Come on.
Hey, I'm going too.
Come on, I'm going too.
It's that time, I'm going to get you.
Yes.
Otre, Sol, I'm going to get you.
He doesn't want to leave.
It's him, it's me.
I'm going with you.
He's probably the brand.
How about you?
You asked for it, it's the plan,
the plan, actually.
Very good.
Get back to work.
Yes, but he's Italian.
Yes.
He'd better be Italian.
Then you call scored taker.
But...
But.
Come on.
Torrante, maybe...
There are no men worth men.
This is a thing of men.
There are no places for women.
Torrante, this can help.
What is this?
A red-haired and mortified woman.
A shuriken.
A shuriken?
A shuriken, a ninja star.
Well, come on, baladita.
Come on.
Demonstration.
Two shits less.
Come on, grab the wings.
Come on, come on.
Who are you?
Police.
Routine procedure.
You'll have to answer some questions.
Hey!
My vase!
You almost got me, Ramírez, damn it.
Look what you've done.
Well, you didn't leave it there,
ma'am.
Well, and what have you come for?
If this case is already in the hands of my
niece's fiancé, Commissioner Torrante.
Torrante?
Yes.
José Luis Torrante?
Do you know him?
Ugh, bloody piece.
But ma'am, how can you think that that
bitch belongs to the body?
But what are you telling me?
He was expelled years ago.
Besides, that man is devoid of his mental
faculties.
Ramírez, leave that bucket, damn it.
I'm looking for evidence.
Evidence?
Look what you're forcing her to do.
Well, it doesn't seem like you're forcing
her to do much, huh?
This must be the boss.
Careful.
I don't like the way you're doing things.
I've brought the money personally,
because of the insecurity you've created
me these days.
The money?
It's all under control.
Controlled?
What is that girl doing here?
This is not a college party.
Come on, Farrelly is about to arrive.
Let's go, occupy positions.
Come on.
We have to get that suitcase.
More than anything, to screw up the
operation.
But, aren't we going to stop them?
Yes, that too.
Torrente, look what you've brought.
What is this?
It's a remote control pump.
I made it by hand.
I thought it might be useful.
Damn it.
I saw the car outside.
You can put it there.
So when Farrelly comes with the drug,
we'll load it.
And in passing, we'll block the exit.
So that those rats can't hear.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, pick it up.
Put it.
With your balls.
Come on.
Shit.
That must be Farrelly.
What the fuck.
Well...
We'll blow up the cars at the exit.
What
have you done?
It's a trap.
Where did you move?
It's a trap!
A trap!
Put it down!
Picking upát I have all guns.
I have the bullet.
Don't move.
Put the gun down.
Guards!
We have to take advantage of the
confusion.
The briefcase.
You have to go for the briefcase.
And why me?
What do you mean why you?
Get the hell out of here.
Come on!
Come on, move!
Come on, fuck!
The briefcase!
They took the briefcase!
Carlitos!
Run!
Let's go!
No!
My mother and my cousin!
Your mother is dead!
Your cousin is a whore, man!
I have the money, let's go!
Come on, let's go!
No!
Let me go!
Dude, are you stupid?
It's 50 kilos!
Come on, I'll give you 10%!
Let me go!
Get the fuck out of here, dude!
This operation has been the great shut-up!
Bring the girl.
If you don't get my money back,
there won't be a place on Earth where you
can hide!
That's it!
You have 10 minutes.
I'll wait for you in the locker room.
Let's go!
Hold on!
Horror,
call 38CGT.
National manufacturing.
It's a victory.
Now we have to find Doria's office.
Is she fucking crazy?
I'll shit your fucking ass!
You are a fucking bitch!
I don't know who you are, but you are
going to pay for all of this.
Where is the money!
Raffy!
I'm coming in!
You're not going to let me go.
He's back.
Say hi to your cousin.
Let's go.
Paro!
Quiet!
Do you want this, Paro?
Drop the gun.
Leave it there.
Always in the middle.
Say goodbye to life, kid.
No!
This is hell.
Come on, let's go.
Torrente!
How are you?
Take care of my father's burial.
How he lived.
With dignity.
And remember, kid, that in life there is
something more important than being a cop.
And that is...
being Spanish.
Will it be okay?
We've been trying to dismantle this gang
for two years.
I don't know how you got it, but
congratulations.
Thank you.
There's only one thing.
The money.
The money?
It's for you.
Take it easy.
Shhh!
You bastards!
To Torremolinos!
To Torrente!
Number 3 The
For For
For For For For For For For For For For
For What you have, you've been looking
for, and it is that your roll has expired.
Why do you want so much money if you don't
have a true friend?
Where does Torrente go?
Always swimming against the current.
There is no Sweden there.
You are no
longer what you were.
Where does
Torrente go?
How can you be such a bad person?